bigcrumbs.com 2007-12-24

# BigCrumbs.com - Get Cash Back When You Shop. Earn Cash When Others Shop.

## BigCrumbs.com completely respects your privacy.

**Information We Collect**  
BigCrumbs.com requires relevant contact and other information in order to facilitate its service offerings. This generally includes your name and contact information such as e-mail and postal mail addresses. 

In the course of conducting its business, BigCrumbs.com naturally compiles purchase information, such as the time of purchase, the retailer, and the purchase amount. 

_BigCrumbs.com does NOT receive your credit card number or other personal information that you submit at our featured retailers' websites_. We receive only information regarding transactions so that we may credit purchases to your BigCrumbs.com account. In some cases, retailers provide us with the actual product or service purchased. We do NOT use or share this additional information. 

**Our Information Sharing Policy**  
BigCrumbs.com does not now, nor will it ever sell or rent any personal information that you share with BigCrumbs.com. 

BigCrumbs.com also does not otherwise share personally identifiable information (such as your e-mail address, other contact information, or information regarding your purchases), except as necessary to facilitate payment processing or other service fulfillment operations through third-party partners. In this event, only the minimum information required will be communicated to such third-party providers. 

The only exceptions to our policy of not sharing member information are: If BigCrumbs.com is required to do so by law. If ownership of BigCrumbs.com is transferred, at which point it will be necessary to transfer all information to the new owner(s). 

**How We Use Your Information**  
We use your information to facilitate our program offerings. For instance, we use your e-mail address to send your payments. 

We may also use the information that you provide to send you updates, news, and other information regarding BigCrumbs.com. Any correspondence that we send will provide you with information and links on how to opt-out, in the event that you no longer wish to receive such correspondence. 

BigCrumbs.com reserves the right to send you important, non-promotional correspondence regarding your account, even if you have opted out of our other mailings. 

**What Are Cookies?**  
Cookies are small text files that a website sends to your web browser. The next time your browser requests information from the website, it sends the information in the cookie back to that website. 

**How Are Cookies Used?**  
Cookies are frequently used to keep track of how many times a user visits a site and to enhance a visitor's experience. For instance, some websites use cookies to recognize you when you return and customize your visit. 

**Does BigCrumbs.com Use Cookies?**  
Yes, BigCrumbs.com uses cookies to recognize you upon return so that we may restore certain features, such as the retailers you select as your favorites. We also use cookies to allow you to shop and receive credit without having to log in each time you visit BigCrumbs.com. This is provided as a convenience for our members. 

When you logoff from BigCrumbs.com, you have the option of deleting this cookie so that you won't be recognized upon your next visit. 

Our featured retailers use cookies to track visits to BigCrumbs.com and to track purchases made by BigCrumbs.com visitors, thereby ensuring that BigCrumbs.com is properly credited. This then allows us to credit our members and it is why cookies should be enabled when using BigCrumbs.com.

Cookies that are set by affiliated retailers when you visit BigCrumbs.com are known as "third-party cookies", since they are not set directly by the site you are visiting (BigCrumbs.com). Cookies that are set by a retailer can only be seen by that retailer. So, for instance, a retailer cannot see another retailer's cookies, nor can a retailer see the cookies that BigCrumbs.com sets. 

**Are Cookies Safe?**  
There are many misconceptions about cookies. Cookies cannot "steal" your personally identifiable information, and they cannot contain any personal information that you did not submit to the website that set the cookie. Also, one website cannot read another website's cookies. So personal information that you enter at one website cannot be seen by another website. 

**How Do I Know If I Have Cookies Enabled?**  
For information on enabling cookies, please see our help page. 

**Featured Retailers' Privacy Policies**  
When you shop through BigCrumbs.com, you are redirected to the websites of our featured retailers, where privacy policies may differ from those of BigCrumbs.com. We are not responsible for the privacy policies of our featured retailers, and we encourage you to understand the privacy policies of any websites to which you submit your personal information.
